

Culinary educator specializing in international cuisine. Experienced with world-renowned tourism and hospitality institutes as an Instructor. Well-versed in numerous hotel industry sectors as a chef. Strong background in education administration, curriculum development, and student management.

VISHAL VISHWANATH APTE

Phone:

+853 62839308

E-Mail:

aptevishal@live.com

Teaching Highlights

- Culinary arts management
- Human nutrition and food
- F & B management
- Food eating behavior
- Gastronomic Tourism
- Food sensory evaluation

Languages

English Hindi

Experience

Instructor – F & B Area 02/2019 to current Macau Institute for Tourism Studies (IFTM), Macau SAR

Sr. Culinary Instructor 02/2015 to 01/2019 **Les Roches Jin Jiang International Hotel Management College**, Shanghai, China

Chef roles 07/2008 to 01/2015 Taj Hotels, Oberoi Hotels, Hyatt Hotels, and Saudi Airlines

Education

Master of Business Administration: General management - 2022 University of the West of Scotland, UK

Bachelor of Science: Tourism and Hotel Management - 2008 **IASE University**, India

Certifications

- Post- Graduate diploma in Culinary Arts and kitchen management
- Certified Hospitality Educator (CHE)
- Certified Food Safety Instructor

References

References available on request